Hello everyone, today I will show you how to crawl the score data of the 2K4 students
for the national high school exam in 2022. Here I will use the website Dân Chí
Here it gives the points of the students, so we can search for the exam point
Here we can enter the name of the student, for example, I am in Đinh Bình, I will enter 27
And behind is the name number 000001, for example, we click to see the result
For example, this is a point of a student with the name number 270001
We click again, when we check about the network
We enter 270000001, we click to see the result
It will show us a file called Search Gradual ATM
Here we have a Request URL, we copy it in here, open it, what is it?
The score is 100, all related to this
The main item here is the student, behind this student it will have the name number, the score
The score is 100, all related to this student, behind this student it will have the name number, the score
Yes, this is the score of the student, below is the statistic score, grey, medium is the variance, and rough year is the appreciating score
Here we use Python to control the score of the students
and it handles the test score very quickly
For example, the exam station in Đinh Bình has 11000 students, we have to use the光 love
We will use a code to clean the test scores
You will be able to process the exam score one by one, in case there is no的時候コ initialization, you know the code
And then we will create a test score to verify the accuracy of the exam scores
we will use the most important dictionary, the most important dictionary about request
import request request this request dictionary, it can request this button
here is the usage of this way it is, then this request part we will get the information
request to send it back, right? Here we will use this request document and
first of all, if you want the thing to be each candidate 1, right, we will definitely
have to run a set of rooms in a set of rooms. For example, the candidate starts at 00001, it's enough for 8
numbers, right? And the last candidate is about 11,000, how much is it here? It depends on the choice,
right? 11000, we will have a set of rooms like this, right? And it will be Scraping
Scraping UAL, we will take the link line, what is it?
Let's take a link line from the request here, this UAL here, open it here, here you
click what do we want for it, it runs in turn, right? Then we have to change the
change is what 27001 this, this, this, this is the number of lines and we will replace it with
the index for X of X, right? The ID string of X, yes, so every time the X runs here, it will
automatically replace it, right? Yes, it's so, the Scraping thing, we choose UAL and send the request, it's
After that, we will give the payload and the header, here I have coded first, the payload and the header
What is the main command? The main command is to calculate this command
The main command is that we will take response by request.request, get scrapping
This is the link we are looking for and the two headers and data are by payload
What is payload? This is when we change it once, then these things will change
This is called payload
That's it for the response. After the response, we will take a variable, for example, if for example, if for
by response.request
Let's take a variable
Let's take the original one, let's take a look at it a little bit, let's see what the default is, it is considered by this
The payload is already 100% by the payload and the student will be all the information contained in this
So the most important school is the student school
We will take the student, right? Does the student have S? No S
And here we will take a variable, what is it?
Uhm
city, now the principal of the studentником is the singleton
Well, the table is a bitchau ah how can we not cope, but I just want myself right?
cafes
If you want to send somebody to the computer, give him a statement that starts with i
if i'm a in com
stuff
the surabhi
U серıyor
xã
xã sûr xã xã xã xã xã xã xã xã xã Book of Hmmm Chemistry is not always good, please note 1 is not always useful if you forgot more. Then pack it to pick up one page. There's no question, is it? If you fill in thisdemo , then it will have adOOOOOOOO all your desx to your computer will make
the total of 12 points, 12 numbers are from the name number, this point will have 12 numbers,
we will get exactly 12, then we like 15 this year 6, 8, 9, 10, two more,
the first thing we start is the name number, the second is what is the math point, the third is the
math point, the fourth is the grammar point, the fifth is the physical point, the sixth is the chemical point,
the seventh is the average or natural
history, the history of geography,
the
next is the nationality and the last is the average of social science,
so I'm missing 12345678910112, I'm missing the biological one, right?
Biological
,
it's ok, overcome the first step to go here, we will check the foreign
attribute for this, the first number that has a capital will be what yes
the degree of the animal's Epaphrodite is found Remember that we have to write it exactly the same over there, is it
exactly like that request your cell phone, I set up an sb became a bit of a shop,?
ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah i won't tell you, i will copy always for a while i will do all i could for free dasr
y
Yes, from the point of Mathematics, I will make the number beautiful so that it looks easy. Mathematics,
Language, Physics, Science, Biology, Normal and Natural points, then after we run
this, what can we use? What can we use? The point is that the
point will be taken by the point's str. Finally, we will print out the point, then
we run this command, then pay attention to the terminal.
Here is the response station student, where am I wrong?
This is where it says, right?
Yes, that's right, Jason is missing the circle.
Yes, now we will run it right away.
Yes, there is still something missing.
Yes, it only runs the first password.
Yes, the basic cycle pattern is here, we will run it right away.
Yes, so it runs out of all the points.
Here is the password.
Here is the password, here are the points, here, these are the games that are
written here that they do not have a test, right?
For example, if they are in the natural scientific school, they will not have to
study social science at the beginning, this is the name.
It just runs the lettres.
Then when it runs out of all the 11,000 students, it will stop.
Here is how I got a call from the country's national media.
But you 24
use.
It's very simple. We can crawl all the points in the same way as other states.
Above is my Python code about crawling data points. See you in the next videos.